[{"id": 1155, "question": "Some nations think they must have more and more babies, more and more people, if they are to remain strong and free. Actually, this is not so. Very often in history, small nations have conquered large ones. It's not so much the size of the army as its organization and the technical level of its weapons. Thus, Greece took over Persia in the 300s B.C., Great Britain took over India in the 1700s, even though Persia and India had far bigger population than Greece and Great Britain. If a nation wishes to avoid being dominated by its neighbors, its best chance is to raise its standard of living and its level of technology. _ can be done best by not allowing its population to grow to such a point that it is sunk in misery and poverty. In fact, the worst way in which a nation can try to avoid bein...\n\nQ: The passage mainly focuses on   _  .", "options": ["why we must control population", "where we can find a solution", "how to stop population growth", "how to become a strong nation"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2199, "question": "Medicine comes in lots of different packages. Painkillers in a tablet can make your headache go away. Antibiotic cream from a tube can prevent your cuts from becoming infected. But can medicine come packaged in chicken eggs? A team of scientists from Scotland say \"yes\". They've engineered special chickens that lay eggs with disease-treating drugs inside. These eggs come from chickens that have been engineered to produce certain drugs inside their egg whites. These drugs are made of molecules called proteins . Animals make thousands of proteins -- they're the main element in skin, hair, milk and meat. Since animals can make proteins easily, they're good candidates for making protein drugs. Researchers have already made cows, sheep and goats produce protein drugs in their milk. But chickens ...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["eating eggs is the best choice for the patients now", "scientists changed the chicken's DNA and put all the drugs in chicken eggs", "we may eat special eggs as drugs when we are sick in the future", "the drugs produce harmful effects on the chicken's bodies"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 715, "question": "Microblogging is a broadcast medium in the form of blogging. A microblog differs from a traditional blog in that its content is typically much smaller, in both actual size and aggregate file size. Microblogs \"allow users to exchange small elements of content such as short sentences, individual images, or video links\". As with traditional blogging, microbloggers post about topics ranging from the simple, such as \"what I'm doing right now,\" to the thematic , such as \"sports cars.\" Commercial microblogs also exist, to promote websites, services and/or products, and to promote collaboration within an organization. Some microblogging services offer features such as privacy settings, which allow users to control who can read their microblogs, or other ways of publishing rights besides entering t...\n\nQ: Microblogging can protect the following privacy EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["deciding the readers of the microblogs", "allowing readers to publish their views", "readers' deleting what a microblog says", "deciding whether readers can enter it"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1666, "question": "Why does a large education nation like China have so few world renowned scientists as the US? Educationists from China and the US try to find out the answer to questions like this at a forum on the basic education strategy. The forum, held recently, was jointly organized by the Education Development Research Center of the Ministry of Education in China and the Postgraduate School of the University of Pennsylvania in the US. It aims to find out similarities and differences that exist between two countries in their educational system. While some educationists in China keep a doubtful eye to the country's educational system in recent years. Their American counterparts give a positive answer to the basic education in China, saying that it is still one of the best in the world. An American educ...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["quality education development in the future", "why China's education cultivates few world masters", "China's good basic education", "genius education at the primary stage"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2575, "question": "Have you ever heard the saying \" _ \"? Here is how a new teacher made friends with the girls and boys in her class on the first day of school. As the bell rang, the teacher smiled at each girl and boy. Then she said in a quiet voice, \"Good morning. How nice it is to have all of you in my class this year. I'd like to know each of you. I am sure we will enjoy working together.\" Everyone felt that she meant what she said because of her sweet voice and her friendly look. She told the girls and boys her name and wrote it on the blackboard. Then she told them some of the things she liked to do and she was hoping to do with them during the year. Then she said to the class, \"Now you know my name and the things I like and I want to know your names and the things you like. Then I will feel that I kno...\n\nQ: A new comer will be your friend if   _  .", "options": ["he always thinks of his old friends", "you ask him to do something", "he knows you", "you talk with him in a friendly way"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1510, "question": "Since my son is getting ready for first grade, I asked a friend where she shops for school supplies. For price and convenience, she had a quick answer: schoolpak.com. Parents can buy items or packaged equipment for all grades. The Generic Elementary School-pak for first through fifth graders, for example, is $23.28. (Teachers can also e-mail their grade's or school's whole list for a price on customized kits . Shipping is free for 75 or more kits) _ Teachers thinks highly of educationalwarehouse.com for its learning tools and games--everything from puzzles and puppets to software and chalks.Classroomdirect.com has great prices on over 10.000 products and a special corner offering even deeper discounts. Pick your lunch box The second-most-difficult back-to-school decision, right after what ...\n\nQ: Both educationalwarehouse.com andTaxadmin.org  _  .", "options": ["are well thought of by teachers", "offer teaching tools", "are tax-free", "can save you some money"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2124, "question": "In America, drivers' education is part of the regular high school curriculum . Every student in his or her second year of high school is required to take a class in driver's education. However, unlike other courses, it is not given during the regular school year. Instead it is a summer course. The course is divided up into two parts: class time for learning laws and regulations, and driving time to practice driving. Class time is not unlike any other class. The students study the basic traffic laws from a text to pass the written driving test that is given to anyone who wants to get a driver's license. Driving time is a chance for the students to get behind the wheel and practice starting steering, backing up, parking, switching lanes, turning corners, and all the other maneuvers required ...\n\nQ: We can infer that the students are required to    _    in their whole driving practice.", "options": ["spend at least six hours driving", "get half an hour driving", "drive for two hour blocks of time", "go out driving for twelve times"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1462, "question": "I have only once been in trouble with the law.The whole process of being arrested and taken to court was a rather unpleasant experience at the time, but it makes a good story now. What makes it rather disturbing was the arbitrary circumstances both of my arrest and my subsequent fate in court. It happened in February about twelve years ago.I had left school a couple of months before that and was not due to go to university until the following October.I was still living at home at the time. One morning I was in Richmond, a suburb of London near where I lived.I was looking for a temporary job so that I could save up some money to go traveling.As it was a fine day and I was in no hurry, I was taking my time, looking in shop windows, strolling in the park, and sometimes just stopping and looki...\n\nQ: The first man who came up to him was   _  .", "options": ["a uniformed policeman", "a policeman in plainclothes", "not a policeman", "a good joker"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2007, "question": "Several years ago I worked in an office, which had a locust tree growing outside the window. It had grown into a tall tree and must have been there for a long time. The tree blocked the view and made the office seem dull, unfortunately this happened to be the room assigned to me and I was depressed by it for quite some time. When the first spring came, everything was green except the locust tree. Secretly, I was very happy because I had thought it had died. One morning when I opened the window for fresh air, I unexpectedly smelt a familiar sweet scent floating into my office but I couldn't name it. Suddenly, I realized it was the locust tree! The tree that I thought dead was blossoming in full glory. From then on, I usually came to the office very early to see dew forming on the locust tre...\n\nQ: What the author wanted to tell us is that   _  .", "options": ["not being delighted for what you have got and not feeling pity on the lost", "think twice before you leap", "treat everything calmly", "cherish what you've owned"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1407, "question": "Rob Coulter worked in the wild of South Africa. He knew the animals, insects, and reptiles of Africa very well. Rob knew them so well that he became careless. One night, while camping alone, Rob reached out to pick up a large piece of wood and felt something bite his arm. Rob didn't think much about it. But a little later, his arm began to ache. When he looked closely at it, he immediately saw two teeth marks in the skin of his arm. He realized that a poisonous snake had bitten him. His pulse became rapid. Rob's mind raced as he thought about what he had to do to survive. Rob knew that he should remain calm, stay still, keep the injured arm below the level of his heart and avoid eating or drinking anything, especially anything with alcohol in it. He also knew that cutting the wound to suck...\n\nQ: How did Rob realize that he had been bitten by a snake?", "options": ["His pulse became rapid.", "His arms began to ache.", "Teeth marks appeared in his arm.", "His skin immediately turned dark."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2853, "question": "It was an extremely hot day. My younger brother Walt and I had decided to go swimming in a deep swimming hole across Mr. Blickez's farm and through some woods, because it would be the only way to cool ourselves down. The only problem with our plan was that this farm was guarded by a huge mean Hereford bull . Mr. Blickez had told us that Elsie was the meanest bull in town, maybe even in the county and we believed in him. But the hotter it got, the more we thought there was something _ about what he said. For one thing, we remembered Mr. Blickez liked telling tall tales; for another, Elsie seemed like a strange name for a bull. Finally, I talked Mom into asking permission for us to walk through the farm, and Mr. Blickez agreed. On our way across the farm, we stopped at the fence to admire th...\n\nQ: When Elsie saw the author's brother, she   _  .", "options": ["tried to attack him", "showed her friendliness", "immediately ran away", "tried to drive him away"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2437, "question": "It is a reply to a letter written by Zhai Mingjun, a 16-year-old girl in the class. The two astronauts thank the student for her concerns and wish the class luck in their future studies. \"I' m so happy that the two space men replied with a few encouraging words,\" said Zhai. Her letter was one of the 10 winning letters taken into space by Fei and Nie, who have succeeded in traveling space in the Sixth Shenzhou Spaceship. Zhai wrote the letter as if she were a younger sister of the astronauts. \"As the single child in my family, I always hoped that I would have an elder brother that I could be proud of,\" Zhai said. \"I thought that the astronauts would be lonely during such a long space trip. I hoped they would feel happy and warm when reading my letter.\" Many of Zhai' s classmates also wrote ...\n\nQ: The best title of this passage can be  _  .", "options": ["The mascot", "A reply from space", "The manned space program", "The letter to the astronauts"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2565, "question": "Ten years ago,Morgan Zuch,a two--year--old girl from Long Island,New York,was diagnosed with leukemia .The day that Morgan's father Rod knew it,he made a promise,\"If my daughter gets better,I will devote the rest of my life to helping others who are in the Same condition.\" Fortunately.Morgan recovered gradually,and since then,Rod and his wife Nancy,have been helping other families with cancer.stricken children through the Morgan Center.It is the country's first preschool for children with cancer. Because of the risk of germs, children with cancer are usually forbidden from playing with other kids.They must spend their days in hospital rooms or lying in bed at home.The Zuchs believed that children with cancer should have the opportunity to play,too. The center offers the kids and their fami...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the text?", "options": ["The kids can share all their toys there.", "The kids can receive free medical care.", "The kids have to keep their hands clean.", "The kids' parents must pay for the supplies."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 217, "question": "Do you find getting up in the morning so difficult that it's painful ? This might be called laziness, but Dr. Kleitman has a new explanation. He has proved that everyone has a daily energy cycle. During the hours when you labour through your work you may say that you're \"hot\". That's true. The time of day when you feel most energetic is when your cycle of body temperature is at its peak . For some people the peak comes during the forenoon. For others it comes in the afternoon or evening No one has discovered why this is so , but it leads to such familiar monologues as : \"Get up, John! You'll be late for work again !\" The possible explanation to the trouble is that John is at his temperature-and -energy peak in the evening. Much family quarrelling ends when husbands and wives realize what t...\n\nQ: If you wants to work more efficiently at your how point in the morning, you should   _  .", "options": ["change his energy cycle", "overcome his laziness", "get up earlier than usual", "go to bed earlier"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 164, "question": "If you had a strange sound in your ear, what would you do? One man in Wales who thought he had a fly in his ear called 999, the emergency services number in Britain. And so did a woman who was worried about her green potatoes. Could she make chips with them? Were they poisonous? She didn't hesitate about calling the local ambulance service to ask. According to a recent report, more than 31,000 non-urgent calls were made to the Welsh Ambulance Service in the last year. Inappropriate calls are a headache for health professionals everywhere. In the US, prank calls to 911 happen on a daily basis. Many callers use apps which hide their identity. But those who try to be funny shouldn't be surprised if the police _ . One man from Colorado was arrested for making more than 1,200 prank calls, accor...\n\nQ: How does the author introduce the topic of the text?", "options": ["By giving examples.", "By telling a story.", "By listing figures.", "By making a comparison."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 760, "question": "We've all heard the phrase \"love is patient\", but one couple in prefix = st1 /Michigan, took this phrase to a whole new level. On Monday, February 13, Willard Mason sat down to talk about his relationship with the love he lost more than 60 years ago. Good fortune and fate recently helped the couple reunite. In 1941, Willard Mason and Llah Ost, both senior 2 students, became engaged to be married and began planning their lives together. But Willard moved away to work at Willow Run Bomber Plant, where he met and fell in love with a woman named Helvi. He broke off his long distance engagement to Llah and married Helvi in 1942. Llah later found love with someone else. Both had happy marriages and raised families. Then, in 2003, Helvi died. A year later, Willard found himself back in his hometo...\n\nQ: What does the writer probably mean by saying the phrase \"love is patient\"?", "options": ["To win love needs a good-natured tolerance of waiting.", "Love can make someone ill in hospital.", "Love can also help one set a world record.", "To win love needs a whole new level of cooking skill"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 241, "question": "Discover Artistic Talents across the Country Redtory, Guangzhou Redtory, established in 2009, is a spacious art district often referred to as Guangzhou's 798. Made up of more than 30 old halls, mostly buildings of red brick, the place was originally built in 1956 as Chinese largest can factory. Some of the rusty machines from the old factory have been kept as art equipment, giving the zone an old charm. Where: No. 128 Yuancun Siheng Road, Tianhe District, Guangzhou Opening hours: Mon-Sun 10:30 am-9 pm Tank Loft, Chongqing This 12,000-square-meter art center was established on the site of a used military tank warehouse . It is the largest contemporary art base in western China, featuring modern exhibition, galleries, design studios and art bookstores. The art zone is located on the campus o...\n\nQ: Which of the following was built first?", "options": ["Redtory, Guangzhou.", "Tank Loft, Chongqing.", "M50, Shanghai.", "798 Art Zone, Beijing."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2246, "question": "Drownings, bicycle injuries, falls, and pedestrian accidents are the most common causes of childhood injury or death. Here's what you need to know to avoid tragedy: * Drowning: Each year, thousands of children die from drowning, with two-thirds of accidents occurring in the summer. To protect kids, parents should install multiple layers of protective devices, with each layer offering another opportunity to avoid a tragedy. Fences, door alarms, pool covers are all somewhat effective individually, but their effectiveness is increased dramatically when used in combination with one another. * Falls: Falls from heights kill 140 children under the age of 15 each year in the United States, and seriously injure three million more, making falls the leading cause of non-deadly injury for this age gr...\n\nQ: What can be concluded from the article?", "options": ["Bicycles cause the most non-delay injuries for children in the US each year", "Pedestrian accidents happen much more frequently than drownings in the US each year", "A combination of fences, door alarms and pool covers can greatly reduce the risks of drowning.", "Children should never be allowed to cross the street on their own."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 573, "question": "In 1955, a man named Raymond Kroc entered a partnership with two brothers named Mcdonald. They operated a popular restaurant in California which sold food that was easy to prepare and serve quickly. Hamburgers, French fries, and cold drinks were the main foods on the limited menu. Kroc opened similar eating places under the same name, \"McDonald's\" and they were a quick success. He later took over the company and today it is one of the most famous and successful \"fast-food\" chains in America and the world. Why was his idea so successful? Probably the most important reason was that his timing was right. In the 1950s, most married women stayed home to keep house and take care of their children. During the 1960s, the movement for equality between men and women and an economy that needed more f...\n\nQ: Which of the following was NOT a reason for Raymond Kroc's success?", "options": ["His partnership with the McDonald brothers.", "A changing economy.", "The back-to-nature movement.", "Women's equality movement."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1735, "question": "Throughout July 1945, the Japanese mainland, from Tokyo on Honshu northward to the coast of Hokkaido, were bombed as if an invasion were about to take place. In fact, something far more threatening was at hand, as the Americans were telling Stalin at Potsdam. In 1939 physicists in the United States had learned of experiments in Germany showing the possibility of atomic power and understood the coming damage of an atomic bomb. On August 2, 1939, Albert Einstein warned President Roosevelt of the danger of Nazi Germany's advances in development of the atomic bomb. Eventually, the U.S. Office of Scientific Research Development was created in June 1941 and given combined responsibility with the War Department in the Manhattan Project to develop a nuclear bomb. After four years of research and d...\n\nQ: What made the U.S. decide to drop the atomic bombs over Japan?", "options": ["Truman's becoming the president of the United States.", "The great destruction power of the atomic bomb.", "Reducing the cost of its lives.", "Not being content with Japan's reply."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 226, "question": "He looked like a pirate. With his handkerchief tied in a knot behind his little nine-year-old head, he looked like a pirate, a sad pirate. The first time little David came to our camp, he was hairless and worn out from medical treatments. He was also very angry. Paul Newman's camp counselors ( ) were hoping to fill David's days with fun and laughter. But David stayed inside himself, wanting to be alone, or in a corner of the cabin. At this camp for children with life-threatening illnesses, we had seen some pretty tough children worn out by cancer recover full of energy despite their illness. But we saw little progress in David no matter what we tried with him. Five days into the eight-day session saw a quiet, sad little pirate. Then something happened on that fifth night. Something at camp...\n\nQ: Seeing David smashing the potato chips, the counselor did the same thing in response because he  _  .", "options": ["would like David to eat more of them", "hoped all the other campers would join", "found it possible to help David release anger", "wanted to show that he was as angry as David"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1138, "question": "Americans have contributed to many art forms, and jazz, a type of music, is one of the art forms started in the United States. Black Americans, who sang and played the music of their homeland, created jazz. Jazz is a mixture of the music of Africa, the work songs the slaves sang, and religious music. Improvisation is an important part of jazz. This is why a jazz song sounds a little different each time it is played. Jazz bands formed in the late 1800s. They played in bars and clubs in many towns and cities of the South, especially New Orleans. New Orleans is an international seaport, and people from all over the world come to New Orleans to hear jazz. Jazz became more and more popular. By the 1920s, jazz was popular all over the United States. By the 1940s, you could hear jazz not only in ...\n\nQ: From the text we can learn that   _  .", "options": ["New Orleans is the place where jazz was very popular", "the American people are all jazz lovers", "jazz is merrily sung by black people when working", "jazz may become less popular as time goes on"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3094, "question": "The U.S. Department of Labor statistics show that there is an oversupply of college trained workers and that this oversupply is increasing. Already there have been more than enough teachers, engineers, physicists, aerospace experts, and other specialists. Yet colleges and graduate schools continue every year to turn out highly trained people to compete for jobs that aren't there. The result is that graduates cannot enter the professions for which they were trained and must take temporary jobs which do not require a college degree. On the other hand, there is a great need for skilled workers of all sorts: carpenters, electricians, mechanics, plumbers, TV repairmen. These people have more work than they can deal with, and their annual incomes are often higher than those of college graduates....\n\nQ: It's implied but not stated in the passage that   _  .", "options": ["many other countries are facing the same problem", "white-collar workers in the US used to make more money than blue-collar workers", "fewer students will prefer to go to college in the future", "the law of supply and demand has a strong effect on American higher education"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 296, "question": "Children today would rather toy with new technologies. The role of children has changed as well as that of teens. The world has truly evolved throughout the years. Today,a typical day in the life of a five year old is entirely different from what it once was. A few decades ago children used to work. They did the kind of work parents do today. Today there are shows on which children are putting pounds of makeup on and have flashing things all over their bodies. This makes a child want to _ all of their imperfections. They think they have to look perfect all the time. Teens have changed as well. My grandma got married when she was thirteen. Girls who had an arranged marriage had no time to play because they were expected to cook, clean,take care of the kids, and do housework every single day...\n\nQ: The author's attitude towards changes of teen's life is   _  .", "options": ["critical", "neutral", "optimistic", "complaining"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2521, "question": "A young man went to a town and worked there. He did not have a wife and a servant did the work in his house. The young man liked laughing a lot. He nailed the servant's shoes to the floor on Monday, and then laughed, because he put his feet in them and fell down. The servant was not angry, but smiled. Then the young man put brushes in his bed on Tuesday. The servant got into bed and hit the brushes with his feet. He was afraid. The young man laughed loudly again. Again the servant was not angry, but smiled. Then on Wednesday the young man said to his servant, \"You're a nice, kind man. I am not going to be unkind to you again.\" The servant smiled and said, \"And I'm not going to put any more mud from the street in your coffee.\"...\n\nQ: Why did the young man stop playing jokes on the servant?", "options": ["Because the servant showed kind and nice behaviour to him", "Because the servant told him the truth", "Because he wanted to be a good man", "Because his father told him to do so"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 623, "question": "Is there anything more important than health?I don't think so.You can't be good at your studies or work when you are ill. If you have a headache,or a bad cough,if you run a high temperature and have a bad cold,I think you should go to the doctor. The doctor will examine your throat,feel your pulse,take your temperature,sound your heart and lungs.After that he will advise some treatment,or some medicine.The only thing you have to do is to follow his advice. Speaking of doctor's advice,I can't help telling you a funny story. An old man came to see the doctor.The man was very ill.He told the doctor about his weakness,memory loss and serious problems with his heart and lungs.The doctor examined him and said there was no medicine for his disease. He told his patient to go to a quiet place for a...\n\nQ: From the last sentence of the passage,we learn the man   _   before the doctor told him not to smoke more than one cigarette a day.", "options": ["was a heavy smoker", "didn't smoke so much", "didn't smoke", "began to learn to smoke"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2924, "question": "Steps Shoes Salon Steps Shoes Salon, 4518 S.Cottage Grove, knows our \"economy is weathering a little storm\" They've discounted winter botts and shoes for their fellow shoes lovers.So step in and save! Hours: 11a.m.to 7 p.m.Monday through Friday; 11 a.m.to 6 p.m.Saturaday; Noon to 5 p.m.the first Sunday of this month (closeed other Sundays).Call 773-548 Jonathan Saunders for Target If you've ever watched a runway shoes and thought \"yeah, that dress would be awesome if it wasn't $ 1,800\", you'll be very pleased to know that British designer Jonathan Saunders has decided to use his powers for good and offer fashion - forward clothing.His collection was inspired by the works of Gustav Klimt, Jackson Pollack and Rothko.The clothing ranges from $ 14.99 to $ 29.99 and is only available until Nove...\n\nQ: Miss Blythe, who will be free at 7 p.m.tonight, might go to_for some purchase.", "options": ["Cinnamon Boutique", "Jonathan Saunders for Target", "Steps Shoe Salon", "Dressing Room Shoes"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3431, "question": "The small coastal town of Broome, in northwest Australia, is a remote village in the vast countryside. There are no traffic jams and hardly any roads. There is only the massive Australian wild land, where some houses are 500 miles apart and some driveways are 50 miles long. There seem to be only two main sources of entertainment out here: the sunset at the beach and Sun Pictures. Sun Pictures is a very different movie theater:The seats are park benches and deck chairs, but you're also welcome to sit on the grass. It is the world's oldest outdoor movie garden. Sun Pictures was built in 1916 on the other side of the globe from Hollywood. All the big films were shipped here and the lonely country was amazed. Broome resident Pearl Hamaguchi has never traveled far from home. But in the Sun Pict...\n\nQ: .Sun Pictures is different from other theaters because   _  .", "options": ["it is the most historical outdoor theater in the world", "the audience can either sit on chairs or on the grass", "it was built by some constructor from Hollywood", "all the films were imported here from Hollywood"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2023, "question": ". Passage 1 Every morning, when we wake up, we have 24 brand-new hours to live. What a gift! We have the capacity to live in a way that these 24 hours will bring peace, joy, and happiness to ourselves and to others. Peace is right here and now, in ourselves and in everything we do and see. The question is whether or not we are in touch with it. We don't have to travel far away to enjoy the blue sky. We don't have to leave our city or even our neighborhood to enjoy the eyes of a beautiful child. Even the air we breathe can be a source of joy. We can smile, breathe, walk, and eat our meals in a way that allows us to be in touch with the abundance of happiness that is available. We are very good at preparing how to live, but not very good at living. We know how to sacrifice ten years for a di...\n\nQ: In Passage 2 lines 8--10, the \"present\" is characterized as    _   .", "options": ["an unavoidable imposition", "an unsolvable puzzle", "a dangerous threat", "a burdensome obligation"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 923, "question": "In ancient Egypt, a shopkeeper discovered that he could attract customers to his shop simply by making changes to its environment. Modern businesses have been following his lead,with more tactics . One tactic involves where to display the goods. Foe example, stores place fruits and vegetables in the first section. They know that customers who buy the healthy food first will feel happy so that they will buy more junk food later in their trip. In department stores, section is generally next to the women's cosmetics section:while the shop assistant is going back to find the right size shoe, bored customers are likely to wander over cosmetics they might want to try later. Besides, businesses seek to appeal to customers' senses. Stores notice that the smell of baked goods encourages shopping, t...\n\nQ: Why do stores usually display fruits and vegetables in the first section?", "options": ["To save customers times.", "To show they are high quality foods.", "To help sell junk food.", "To sell them at discount prices."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2132, "question": "Bruce Jun Fan Lee was born in the hour of the Dragon, between 6 and 8 a.m., in the \"Year of the Dragon\" on November 27, 1940 at the Jackson Street Hospital in San Francisco's Chinatown. Today, a plaque in the hospital's entry remembers the place of his birth. Bruce's birth, in the hour and the year of Dragon, is a powerful symbol in Chinese astrology . It would be a strong indication of the powerful life that was to be lived by Bruce Lee and the explosive influence his life would have on countless others. At the age of three months, Lee Hoi Chuen, his wife Grace and baby Bruce returned to Hong Kong where Bruce would be raised until the age of 18. Probably because of the long ocean voyage and the change in climates, Bruce was not a strong child in his very early years, a condition that woul...\n\nQ: Bruce didn't have a strong body until   _  .", "options": ["he practiced boxing in high school", "he took up kung fu with Master Yip Man", "he won a dancing championship", "he returned to the land of his birth"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2570, "question": "When Steve Jobs was born on Febuary24,1955, in San Francisco , California, his unmarried mother decided to put him for adoption because she wanted a girl. So in the middle of the night, his mother called a lawyer named Paul Jobs and said, \"We have an unexpected baby boy; do you want him?\" But his mother told his future parents to promise that they would send Jobs to college. After Steve Jobs graduated from high school, he went to college but decided to drop out because it was so expensive that he had to sleep on the floor in his friends' rooms. At 20, he and a friend(Steve Wozniak) started a company in a garage on April 1, 1976. Jobs named their company ----Apple in memory of a happy summer he had spent as an orchard in Oregon. After 10 years of hard time and failures, starting from two ki...\n\nQ: What can we learn from what Steve Jobs said?", "options": ["Interest is key to success.", "Hope helps us succeed.", "Attitude is everything.", "Courage goes with confidence."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2738, "question": "While Americans feel worried about how to look after their children and help them grow, French parents are raising happy, well-behaved children without all the anxiety. Pamela Druckerman, an American mother living in Paris, watched carefully as to why French children seem to behave so much better than American children. Let's listen to what she said. While eating at the restaurants in Paris, I noticed the French kids were either sitting in their chairs waiting for their food or eating fish and even vegetables, happy and satisfied. There was no shouting or crying, and there were no pieces of food around their tables. However, my 2-year-old daughter, Beth, took a brief interest in the food. She even threw food everywhere. She couldn't keep herself in her chair and ran around the table. Thoug...\n\nQ: While eating at restaurants in Paris, French kids   _", "options": ["make a lot of noise", "like running around", "behave very well", "only eat what they like"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2747, "question": "Many of you may wonder what else to do besides watching TV or surfing the Internet on weekends.Why not have a picnic? Junior 2 students at Beijing No.4 Middle Schoo1 had a \"King of cooking\" competition* Earlier this month,about 300 students at the schoo1 went to a suburb of Beijing to have the contest.They were divided into 24 groups.Each group had buyers,slicers ,firemakers.washers and cooks. Firemakers faced the most problems during the time.Some of them had no idea how to keep fire burning. \"The fire kept going out.we had to blow at the sparks and put on corn leaves and old newspapers,\"said Wu Mofei,13. \"It took us an hour to make the fire.Our eyes had tears from all the smoke and our faces became dirty,\"he added. When the fires were finally made,the cooks became the busiest people.Huan...\n\nQ: We can infer that Huang Lanye was a   _  in their group", "options": ["buyer", "firemaker", "washer", "cook"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 572, "question": "In 1955, a man named Raymond Kroc entered a partnership with two brothers named Mcdonald. They operated a popular restaurant in California which sold food that was easy to prepare and serve quickly. Hamburgers, French fries, and cold drinks were the main foods on the limited menu. Kroc opened similar eating places under the same name, \"McDonald's\" and they were a quick success. He later took over the company and today it is one of the most famous and successful \"fast-food\" chains in America and the world. Why was his idea so successful? Probably the most important reason was that his timing was right. In the 1950s, most married women stayed home to keep house and take care of their children. During the 1960s, the movement for equality between men and women and an economy that needed more f...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["how and why \"McDonald's\" became successful", "the effect social and economic changes have on people's eating habits", "why Americans prefer natural food", "American eating habits"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 751, "question": "Beijing has started a battle to get rid of \"Chinglish\" (Chinese English).The \"Language Mandarins\" of Beijing have decided that Chinglish is a disease for China's modernizing claim and must be _ before the city hosts the Olympic Games in 2008. A road sign on the Avenue of Eternal Peace (Chang'an Street) ,for example, advises: \"To Take Notice of Safe; The Slippery Are Very Crafty\", a warning that the sidewalk was slippery .Another sign in a Beijing park reads: \"Little grass is smiling slightly, please walk on sidewalk.\" Li Honghai, the city official in charge of the battle, said,\" Linguistic perfection is becoming increasingly important with the rise in the number of the foreigners flowing into the city.\" However, not everyone shares the disdain of the Beijing government for the mixed langua...\n\nQ: We can infer that the English language versions of newspapers   _  .", "options": ["should report the battle above", "should be paid more attention to", "should collect more Chingliah phrases", "should be in duty to teach normal English"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2767, "question": "Hurricane reached the northeastern United States today and caused death and destruction everywhere. The killer storm carried winds of 135 miles per hour. The high winds and heavy rains created extremely dangerous waves. It is not yet known how many people died or were hurt in this storm, but it is said that the numbers will be very high. With the arrival of the tornado season, the National Weather Service is again telling people how to protect themselves from these deadly storms. The winds from tornadoes are the most violent winds on earth. They can blow up to 400 miles per hour. A _ looks like a funnel . It is also very loud. It may sound like a train coming at you. In fact, the winds from a tornado can pick up a train and throw it around. If a tornado is seen in your area, it is very imp...\n\nQ: Which of the following is WRONG about tornados?", "options": ["They look like a funnel.", "They come regularly every year.", "They are the most violent winds on Earth.", "They carry winds of 135 km per hour."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2513, "question": "The interview had been going on for about 20 minutes and everything seems to be going well. Then,suddenly,the interviewer asks an unexpected question,\"Which is more important,law or Dove?\" Job applicants in the West increasingly find themselves asked strange questions like this. And the signs are that this is beginning to happen in China. Employers want people skilled,enthusiastic and devoted. So these are the qualities that any reasonably intelligent job applicants will try to show no matter what his or her actual feelings are. In response,employers are increasingly using questions which try and show the applicant's true personality. The question in the first paragraph comes from a test called the Keirsey Personality Sorter. It is an attempt to discover how people solve problems,rather th...\n\nQ: The writer wrote the passage to  _  .", "options": ["give you a piece of advice on a job interview", "tell you how to meet a job interviewer", "describe the aptitude test", "advise you how to find a job"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1613, "question": "November not only marks the publication of Toni Morrison's eagerly anticipated eighth novel, Love, but it is also the tenth anniversary of her Nobel Prize for Literature. Morrison is the first black woman to receive a Nobel, and so honored before her in literature are only two black men:Wole Soyinka, the Nigerian playwright, poet and novelist, in 1986; and Derek Walcott, the Caribbean-born poet, in 1992. But Morrison is also the first and only American-born Nobel prizewinner for literature since 1962, the year novelist John Steinbeck received the award. Like Song of Solomon, Love is a multigenerational story, revealing the personal and communal Legacy of an outstanding black family. As Morrison scholars will tell you, Love is the third volume of a literary master's trilogy investigating th...\n\nQ: The novel Love mainly describes   _  .", "options": ["the best-known vacation spot for blacks", "the life of an outstanding black family under slavery", "the miserable experience of the five women in Harlem", "the memories of five women about Bill Cosey"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 381, "question": "To err is human. To blame the other guy is even more human. Common sense is not all that common. Why tell the truth when you can come up with a good excuse? These three popular misquotes are meant to be jokes, and yet they tell us a lot about human nature .To err, or to make mistakes, is indeed a part of being human, but it seems that most people don't want to accept the responsibility for the problem. Perhaps it is the natural thing to do .The original quote about human nature went like this: \" To err is human, to forgive, divine .\"This saying mirrors an ideal people should be forgiving of others' mistakes. Instead, we tend to do the opposite -find someone else to pass the blame on to. However, taking responsibility for something that went wrong is a making of great maturity. Common sense...\n\nQ: According to tile passage, which of following seems the most human?", "options": ["To search for truth.", "To achieve one's ideal", "To make fun of others' mistakes.", "To criticize others for one's own error."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2662, "question": "Try imagining what the world will be like in the year 3000. Some serious thinkers are starting to imagine just that. Bart: I don't know that present-day electronic chips are, but some sort of chips -- I'd guess maybe plastic. Our three-pound brain is definitely a wonder, perhaps the greatest wonder of natural biology. In this coming century, we'll be re-engineering the brain a piece at a time, first with implants and finally engineering an complete replacement. There's no question that in the distant future we'll play the music of the mind on instruments different from the current ones. So, yes, chips are our destiny . Edward: In 3000 perhaps the biggest difference from today is that there will be no more men. Females can have female children, without any need for men. In about ten years, ...\n\nQ: According to Bart, the brain may be the greatest wonder in the future because   _  .", "options": ["it may weigh as much as 3 pounds", "it may be driven by plastic chips", "it may be replaced by robots", "it may play the music of the mind"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 86, "question": "When was the last time someone did something unexpectedly nice for you? Not someone you knew, but a total stranger? It's happened to me a few times, but two instances really stand out. A few years ago, I was dining out with a person who kept going on and on about himself, completely unaware of the fact that I was sitting there in misery . It wasn't his company that disappointed me. I was recovering from a bad grade in my study. I could have collapsed in tears right there at the table. When we picked up the check, the waitress said, \"Your meal was already paid for.\" My friend and I didn't have a clue how it happened. Then I remembered a man coming in out of the corner of my eye. He was dressed in mostly white, sat down at the bar, had a glass of wine, stayed for maybe ten minutes and then l...\n\nQ: Why did the author say she was in misery?", "options": ["Because she got into trouble with her friend.", "Because she couldn't enjoy her meal quietly.", "Because her friend complained so much.", "Because she was doing poorly in her study."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1773, "question": "Who doesn't love sitting beside a cosy fire on a cold winter's night ? Who doesn't love to watch flames curling up a chimney? Fire is one of man's greatest friends, but also one of his greatest enemies. Many big fires are caused by carelessness. A lighted cigarette thrown out of a car or train window or a broken bottle lying on dry grass can start a fire. Sometimes, though, a fire can start on its own. Wet hay can begin burning by itself. This is how it happens: the hay starts to rot and begins to give off heat which is trapped inside it. Finally, it bursts into flames. That's why farmers cut and store their hay when it's dry. Fires have destroyed whole cities. In the 17th century, a small fire which began in a baker's shop burnt down nearly every building in London. Moscow was set on fire...\n\nQ: Which of the following statement is not true ?", "options": ["Fires still cause much damage now although there are modern fire - fighting", "Fires cause less damage in the country than in the city .", "Fire can be man's good friend and also great enemy .", "One should be careful not to throw a lighted cigarette everywhere ."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 497, "question": "Every spring Beijing is choked by huge sandstorms.The sky turns a strange and frightening yellow colour as clouds of sand sweep down from the deserts of Mongolia and north-western China.Strong winds blow up the dust and cover everything in sight--in 2006,a storm dumped 330,000 tonnes of dust on Beijing in one night. The number of sandstorms has grown alarmingly over the years as the deserts have expanded.This is partly man-made and partly because of climate .Many grasslands have been overgrazed by sheep and goats,or ploughed up,leaving the soil dangerously exposed.Too much water has been taken out of rivers,and the situation is made worse by increasingly long-lasting droughts that have affected the northern half of China as the climate grows warmer and drier.The result is probably the wors...\n\nQ: All the following are the reasons for the expansion of the deserts EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["the soil of the grasslands is exposed", "too much water in rivers has been used", "it doesn't rain for a long time", "the climate in northern China is colder and drier"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1625, "question": "On October 12, 1989, some Chinese scientists were working at the computers to look for information they needed. Suddenly they saw a lot of very bright spots crossing the computers's screens. At the same time the computers were working much slower. To find out what was happening they stopped their work to check some parts of the computers. To their horror, they found out that most of their stored information was got rid of by computer viruses ! Obviously all these computers had been infected by computer viruses. It is said that the computer viruses were made by a group of young men fond of playing tricks. They all had excellent education. They created the viruses just to show their intelligence . These kinds of computer viruses are named Jerusalem Viruses. These viruses can stay in computer...\n\nQ: The most serious damage caused by the viruses is that  _  .", "options": ["the computer's functions are lowered", "the normal programs are damaged", "all the information stored in the computers is gone", "the computers infected by the viruses can no longer be used"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1567, "question": "Sports, drama, and a variety of organizations keep students busy during high school. Where do they find the money to do these things? Not everyone gets it from Mommy and Daddy. Most have to pay for these activities. Some adults question if high school students should have jobs. Some people worry that teens with after-school jobs will struggle to find time for homework. Actually, the responsibility of having a job helps teens prioritize their time. Many jobs take only a couple of hour shifts on weeknights. According to a survey, 86 percent of high school students have an after-school, weekend or summer job and students who work between 10 and 20 hours per week during the school year have statistically higher grades-point averages than those who do not work at all. Those who work in high sch...\n\nQ: The author's father advised him to   _  .", "options": ["learn how to use money wisely", "earn money to get what he wants", "work hard to have a bright future", "take part in after-school activities"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2599, "question": "Chinese President Hu Jintao, on his way to talks with President George W. Bush in prefix = st1 /Washington, on Tuesday met with Bill Gates. After the meeting with Gates, the world's richest man, at Microsoft's headquarters, Hu restated that China would move against software pirates all the time. At Microsoft Corp.'s campus, Hu said on Tuesday he admired what Microsoft Chairman Bill Gates had achieved. He also sought to reassure Gates that China is serious about protecting intellectual property rights . \"Because you, Mr. Bill Gates, are a friend of China, I'm a friend of Microsoft,\" Hu said. \"Also, I am dealing with the operating system produced by Microsoft every day,\" he added, to laughter. Gates responded: \"Thank you, it's a fantastic relationship,\" and then said: \"And if you ever need a...\n\nQ: What measure is not mentioned to protect intellectual property rights?", "options": ["Moving against software pirates", "creating and enforcing laws", "increasing Microsoft's investment in China", "requiring Chinese computer makers to load legal software on their machines"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 863, "question": "Nathan's second-hand bike was good enough to get him anywhere he wanted to go. Of course, it couldn't match Tim's in a normal speed race, but all the fancy gears in the world wouldn't get you up Black Mountain. It was so steep in places that you had to get off your bike and push. On this particular afternoon, the odds were all on Nathan's side. First, he was stronger. Tim had always been thin, but recently he'd started to grow so fast that his arms and legs were like pieces of spaghetti. As well as being considerably fitter than his friend, Nathan knew the shortcuts up prefix = st1 /BlackMountain. So when Nathan accepted the challenge, he was sure he'd win. He nearly always did, in competitions with Tim. That was what was strange. Tim was so competitive, and yet he wasn't any good at physi...\n\nQ: The quotation \" the odds were all on Nathan's side\" means that   _  .", "options": ["Tim would not try very hard in the race", "Tim had not yet grown as big as Nathan", "Nathan had a greater chance of winning the challenge", "Nathan had more friends who thought he would win"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 289, "question": "BEIJING - China will build a nation-wide network within three to five years to monitor the impact of air pollution on health, a latest step to deal with a _ smog crisis in big cities, an official said. A total of 43 monitoring spots will be set up in 16 provinces and municipalities frequently engulfed by smog so as to facilitate research on air pollutants in different regions, the impact on the health of vulnerable groups and the study of related diseases, said Xu Dongqun, an official with the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention. With funds allocated by the central government, the study will provide reference for preventive efforts to reduce the PM 2.5, Xu said. Thick and dangerous smog have hit 17 provinces and municipalities with a population of 600 million this year. One o...\n\nQ: China will take measures to deal with air pollution except  _  .", "options": ["China recently issued a 1.75 trillion-yuan (284.2 billion U.S. dollars) plan", "set up monitoring spots in 16 provinces and municipalities", "improveliving standard", "improve the air in major city clusters"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3006, "question": "People bury treasure to stop other people from taking it. They choose a quiet place, dig a deep hole and bury the treasure in it. Then they make a map of where the treasure is or write down other clues that will help them or someone else to find it again. In Britain a few years ago, a writer wrote about some treasure that he had buried. He put clues in the story to help readers find it. Thousands of people hunted for the treasure. They dug holes all over Britain, hoping to find it. One of the most popular adventure stories ever written is Robert Louis Stephenson's \"Treasured Island\", an exciting story about a young boy, Jim Hawkins, who is captured by pirates and later finds some buried treasure. Then there is the true story about a man who had to travel overseas for a year. He did not tru...\n\nQ: \"Treasure Island\"    _    .", "options": ["is a story about pirates.", "is about the adventures of Jim Hawkins.", "is the most popular story ever written.", "is a well-known fairy tale."], "answer": 1}]